Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Photographs
  - Photographs - Events
    - Awards – March 20-22, 1976 – Chicago – National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award (Box 128, Folder 30.)
    - Awards – May, 1976 -- Chicago– National Association of Broadcasters Distinguished Service Award – Escorts (all NBC Affiliates) Ancil Payne; Robert Ferguson; Jack Harris; JG; Louis Read; Clair McCullough; Elmo Ellis; Hod Grams (Box 128, Folder 31.)
    - Awards – undated – Award dinner for Julian Goodman (Box 128, Folder 32.)
    - Television Pioneers of America Award – Julian Goodman, Lewis Schallenberger; James Hagerty; Bryson Rash, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 33.)
    - circa 1950s Public Relations Seminar – 12th Naval Reserve, Undated (Box 128, Folder 34.)
    - The Great Debates #2 – John F. Kennedy and Richard Nixon – Julian Goodman and Fred Slingland, October 7, 1960 (Box 128, Folder 35.)
    - Julian Goodman and unidentified – National Association of Broadcasters, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 36.)
    - Washington D.C. -- Radio and TV Correspondents Annual Dinner – Vice President Hubert H. Humphrey, March 7, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 37.)
    - Washington D.C. – Radio and TV Correspondents Annual Dinner – Lyndon B Johnson, Julian Goodman and others, March 7, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 38.)
    - Washington D.C. – Radio and TV Correspondents Annual Dinner – Richard Nixon and Julian Goodman, March 7, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 39.)
    - Washington D.C. – Radio and TV Correspondents Annual Dinner – Richard Nixon, Edward P. Morgan, Julian Goodman (Nixon hands gavel to Julian Goodman), March 7, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 40.)
    - Washington D.C. – Radio and TV Correspondents Annual Dinner – Julian Goodman and unidentified others, March 7, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 41.)
    - Hawaii Trip – Julian Goodman and Betty Goodman, May 11-13, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 42.)
    - Commencement Speech at Western Kentucky University; “A Time to Grow” – Kelly Thompson, Herbert J. Smith, Carol Cole Strong, Julian Goodman, August 5, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 43.)
    - Julian Goodman Testifying before congress, August 23, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 44.)
    - Chicago – Radio and Television News Directors Association (RTNDA) – Julian Goodman with unidentified, October 1, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 45.)
    - Miami – Orange Bowl Committee Annual President’s Dinner (OBIE Award to JG) with William T. Lantaff; Alex Biscarre, May 2, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 46.)
    - Berlin – Visit to overseas staff – Julian Goodman and Robert Kintner (Berlin); Lord Mayor Heinrich Albertz (West Berlin), August 20-31, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 47.)
    - Paris, Arc de Triomphe – Visit to overseas staff – Julian Goodman, John Rich, and Robert Kintner, August 23-26, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 48.)
    - Advertisers Club of Cincinnati, October 11, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 49.)
    - New York -- Soap and Detergent Association, January 26, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 50.)
    - Republican National Convention in Miami Beach, Florida, August 5 – 8, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 51.)
    - Chicago – Democratic National Convention – Julian Goodman with Walter Scott and NBC Crew, August 23-31, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 52.)
  - Photographs – Events
    - Chicago – Democratic National Convention – NBC Executives; Julian Goodman, Reuven Frank, David Adams, Walter Scott, Don Durgin, August 23 – 31, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 1.)
    - London – Reception at Claridge’s Hotel for Julian and Betty Goodman and Ray Scherer, April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 2.)
    - London – Reception at Claridge’s Hotel for Julian and Betty Goodman and Ray Scherer (Negatives), April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 3.)
    - London – Reception at Claridge’s Hotel for Julian and Betty Goodman and Ray Scherer (Negatives), April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 4.)
    - London – NBC Event in Goldsmith Hall – Reuven Frank, Julian Goodman, and unidentified, April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 5.)
    - London – NBC Event in Goldsmith Hall, April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 6.)
    - London – NBC Event in Goldsmith Hall (Negatives), April 23, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 7.)
    - Sports/Baseball – Julian Goodman with Mickey Mantle, Mr. and Mrs. Bowie Kuhn, Carl Lindemann, Cal Hubbard, Red Schoendienst, Walter Scott, Mr. and Mrs. Kurt Gowdy, Chub Feeney, Mr. and Mrs. Michael Bluke, October 16, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 8.)
    - Tryall, Jamaica -- TV Board of Delegates – Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, Reuven Frank, Walter Scott, Herbert Schlosser, C.E. Burnett, others unidentified, November 16-22, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 9.)
    - Tryall, Jamaica -- TV Board of Delegates – Julian Goodman, Carl Lindemann, Don Durgin, November 16-22, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 10.)
    - Tryall, Jamaica -- TV Board of Delegates – Wilson C. Wearn, Herbert Schlosser, Theresa Durgin, Don Durgin, November 16-22, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 11.)
    - Tryall, Jamaica -- TV Board of Delegates – unidentified, November 16-22, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 12.)
    - New York – International Radio and Television Society Gold Medal Awarded to Julian Goodman, March 9, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 13.)
    - Atlanta – All Star Game – Governor Jimmy Carter, Bill Bartholomew, William Salatich, Bowie Kuhn, July 25, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 14.)
    - Atlanta – All Star Game – Peachtree Golf Club – William Salatich and other unidentified, July, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 15.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Julian Goodman and Johnny Carson, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 16.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Johnny Carson, Joanna Carson, Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, David Tebet at head table, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 17.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Carson and Goodman with the cake, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 18.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, Mr. and Mrs. Don Durgin, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 19.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Julian Goodman with David Tebet and unidentified others, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 20.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Joanna (Holland) Carson, Johnny Carson, Julian Goodman, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 21.)
    - Tonight Show/Johnny Carson 10th Anniversary Celebration – Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, Jack Benny, Dick Martin, September 29, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 22.)
    - Chicago -- Cosmopolitan Chamber of Commerce Luncheon – Harold Grumhaus (Chicago Tribune), Bertel W. Daigre, Arthur M. Wood, Emmett Dedmon, December 12, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 23.)
    - Election Coverage – Julian Goodman with David Adams, Reuven Frank and unidentified, November 7,1972 (Box 129, Folder 24.)
    - Meet the Press 25th Anniversary – Senator Hubert Humphrey, Julian Goodman, David Adams, Robert Sarnoff, Lawrence Spivak, Senator Edmund Muskie, January 17, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 25.)
    - Meet the Press 25th Anniversary – Senator Edward Kennedy, Julian Goodman, Lawrence Spivak, January 17, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 26.)
    - Meet the Press 25th Anniversary – NBC Executives – David Adams, Don Durgin, Robert Sarnoff, Lawrence Spivak, Richard Wald, Reuven Frank, January 17, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 27.)
    - Meet the Press 25th Anniversary – Julian Goodman and unidentified others, January 17, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 28.)
    - Affiliates TV Board of Delegates – J.S. Sinclair; Harold Froelich; H. Ray McGuire; William Roberson; M.C. Greiner; Wilson Wearn; Ancil Payne; Fred Paxton; Don Durgin; David C. Adams; Robert Ferguson; Julian Goodman, April 3, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 29.)
    - (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) AASCU/Western Kentucky University – Dero Downing, Harold Hyde, Betty Goodman, Julian Goodman and others, November 1973 (Box 129, Folder 30.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception – Julian Goodman with John Rich and others, October 7, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 31.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception – Julian Goodman with John Rich and others, October 7, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 32.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception -- Julian Goodman with John Rich and others, October 7, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 33.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception, October 7, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 34.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception, October 7, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 35.)
  - Photographs – Events
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Reception, October 7, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 1.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – The Conference, October 7, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 2.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly -The Conference, October 7, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 3.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union Assembly – Broadcast by Julian Goodman in NHK Studios, October 7, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 4.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union General Assembly-Broadcast by Julian Goodman in NHK Studios, October 5-12, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 5.)
    - Tokyo – Asian Pacific Broadcasting Union General Assembly, October 5 -12, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 6.)
    - Round Hill, Montego Bay, Jamaica – TV Board of Delegates – Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, Don and Theresa Durgin, Wilson Wearn, November 18-22, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 7.)
    - WTIC 10th Anniversary – Julian Goodman with Ella Grasso and Robert S. Tyrol, February 10, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 8.)
    - New York - Anti-Defamation League of B’nai B’rith, December 10, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 9.)
    - Chicago -- Ex-Chairmen of NBC Affiliates Board – Robert Ferguson, Hod Grams, Julian Goodman, Louis Read, Jack Harris, March 21-23, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 10.)
    - U.S. Government Luncheon – JG; Clair McCullough; Louis Read; Jack Harris; Robert Ferguson; Hod Grams;, Elmo Ellis; Ancil Payne, May 6, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 11.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Senator Hubert Humphrey with Julian Goodman, David Adams, Herbert Schlosser, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 12.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Henry Kissinger with David Adams, Herb Schlosser, Julian Goodman, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 13.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Senator Mike Mansfield with David Adams, Herbert Schlosser, Julian Goodman, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 14.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Rep. Harley Staggers with Julian Goodman and Herbert Schlosser, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 15.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Richard E. Wiley with Herb Schlosser and Julian Goodman, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 16.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Ambassador Ardeshir Zahedi with Julian Goodman and Herb Schlosser, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 17.)
    - Washington, D.C. – NBC 50th Anniversary Celebration Reception – Julian Goodman, Herbert Schlosser, with unidentified guests, May 10, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 18.)
    - Madison Square Garden, New York – Democratic National Convention – Julian Goodman with Herb Schlosser and unidentified others, July 12-15, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 19.)
    - Ithaca College, Ithaca, NY – Julian Goodman Speech, October 22, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 20.)
    - Ithaca College, Ithaca, NY – Julian Goodman Speech, October 22, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 21.)
    - Trip to People’s Republic of China, Japan, Hong Kong – Julian Goodman, Betty Goodman, Richard Wald, July 18-30, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 22.)
    - Trip to People’s Republic of China, Japan, Hong Kong, July 18-30, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 23.)
    - Jockey Gold Cup Dinner – Julian Goodman with Bill Creasy, Sigmund Sommers, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 24.)
    - Friar’s Dinner in New York for David Brinkley and Walter Cronkite – Mayor Ed Koch, Julian Goodman, Pia Lindstrom, NY Attorney General Lefkowitz, Brock Adams, May 5, 1978 (Box 130, Folder 25.)
    - Bowling Green, Kentucky – Western Kentucky University Appreciation Dinner – Julian Goodman with Harriet and Dero Downing, December 14, 1978 (Box 130, Folder 26.)
    - Washington Journalism Conference – Julian Goodman, Austin Kiplinger, Ancil Payne, June 7, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 27.)
    - University of Georgia School of Journalism/Advisory Board – George Gerbner, November 1-3, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 28.)
    - Kentuckians of New York – Harold H. Helm, Senator Wendell Ford, November 15, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 29.)
    - Kentucky Department of Commerce – Harold Helm, June 25, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 30.)
    - Kentucky (?) -- Julian Goodman with others unidentified, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 31.)
    - Kentuckians Dinner – Harold Helm; Phyllis George Brown; Gov. John Y. Brown, December 8, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 32.)
    - Convention Luncheon, Undated (Box 130, Folder 33.)
    - Overseas Press Club (possibly August 1967), Undated (Box 130, Folder 34.)
  - Photographs - Unidentified Events
    - Late 1950s/Early 1960s (Box 130, Folder 35.)
    - Early 1960s (Box 130, Folder 36.)
    - Washington, D.C., 1960s (Box 130, Folder 37.)
    - Jim Curtis, Photographer (Kentucky), undated (Box 130, Folder 38.)
    - Julian Goodman, Walter Scott and others, undated (Box 130, Folder 39.)
    - late 70s (?) – Chicago (?), undated (Box 130, Folder 40.)
    - sports – Superbowl (?) – Julian Goodman and son (?) – Jennifer Edwards (played Heidi), undated, after 1968 (?) (Box 130, Folder 41.)
    - Julian Goodman, Walter Scott, Carl Lindemann, others, undated (Box 130, Folder 42.)
    - Julian Goodman, Herb Schlosser, other, undated (Box 130, Folder 43.)
    - Julian Goodman, David Adams, Walter Scott, others, late 1970s (Box 130, Folder 44.)
- Flat Boxes – Oversize material
  - Flat Box - Photographs
    - Earth from space photo (Box 131, Folder 1.)
    - Julian Goodman and John Chancellor (Box 131, Folder 2.)
    - “Bryson Rash on the Floor” Convention coverage (Box 131, Folder 3.)
    - Republican national convention coverage (Box 131, Folder 4.)
    - Julian Goodman, Don Durgin, Walter Scott, Richard Nixon, Reuvan Frank, David Adams and two unidentified men in an office meeting. (Photo includes pasted on comedic caption), 1971 (Box 131, Folder 5.)
    - Julian Goodman giving a speech (with Robert Kintner) (Box 131, Folder 6.)
    - Julian Goodman, Herbert Schlosser, and two unidentified men at a black tie event (Box 131, Folder 7.)
    - Julian Goodman, William McAndrews, William Salatich, and two unidentified men in the crowd of a sporting event (Box 131, Folder 8.)
    - All-star game in Milwaukee –Julian Goodman, Henry Kissinger, Herbert Schlosser, and unidentified woman and an unidentified man, July 15,1975 (Box 131, Folder 9.)
    - All-star game in Milwaukee –Julian Goodman, Henry Kissinger, Herbert Schlosser, and unidentified woman and an unidentified man, July 15,1975 (Box 131, Folder 10.)
    - All-star game in Milwaukee –Julian Goodman, Henry Kissinger, Herbert Schlosser, and unidentified woman and an unidentified man – July 15,1975 – Henry Kissinger pitching the baseball from the stands (Box 131, Folder 11.)
    - Julian Goodman and Robert Sarnoff at a race track (Box 131, Folder 12.)
    - Convention coverage (?)– Unidentified man on telephone call (Box 131, Folder 13.)
    - Convention coverage (?)–Press taking photographs (Box 131, Folder 14.)
    - Convention coverage (?)–Television control room (Box 131, Folder 15.)
    - Convention coverage (?)– Silhouette of Julian Goodman in front of TV control room (Box 131, Folder 16.)
    - Convention coverage (?) – Julian Goodman in control room (Box 131, Folder 17.)
    - Convention coverage (?) – Chet Huntley and David Brinkley (Box 131, Folder 18.)
    - Signed comic from Chet Huntley – “Well, you won’t have Chet Huntley to kick around anymore” (Box 131, Folder 19.)
    - Julian Goodman conversing with unidentified woman (Box 131, Folder 20.)
    - Julian Goodman conversing with unidentified woman (Box 131, Folder 21.)
    - Julian Goodman portrait circa mid 1970s (5) (Box 131, Folder 22.)
    - Julian Goodman blooper portrait “Hello, Stanley. We’re always glad to see you” (Box 131, Folder 23.)
    - NASA – film strip negatives (Box 131, Folder 24.)
  - Flat Box - Newspapers
    - Envelope addressed to Julian Goodman (Box 132, Folder 1.)
    - The Saturday Evening Post – “Valley of Despair” –, August 18, 1945 (Golf course) (Box 132, Folder 2.)
    - The New York Times, Friday, January 8, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 3.)
    - New York Post, Friday, November 22, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 4.)
    - New York Herald Tribune – “How TV and Radio Flashed News”, Saturday, November 23, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 5.)
    - The New York Times – “Kennedy’s Body Lies in White House; Johnson at Helm with Wide Backing; Police say Prisoner is the Assassin”, Sunday, November 24, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 6.)
    - The New York Times – Section 2, Sunday, November 24, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 7.)
    - The New York Times -- Section 3, Sunday, November 24, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 8.)
    - The Sunday Herald Tribune, November 24, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 9.)
    - The Sunday Herald Tribune – ”The Kennedy Choice; The Nation’s Future”, November 24, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 10.)
    - The New York Times – Television section, Sunday, December 1, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 11.)
    - Television – “On the Beach at Waikiki, NBC Style”, June 1966 (Box 132, Folder 12.)
    - Fame, 1972 (Box 132, Folder 13.)
    - The Saturday Evening Post with Today Show piece, Sept.-Oct. ‘73 (Box 132, Folder 14.)
    - The New York Times –“Bradshaw’s Mandate at RCA”, Monday, January 26, 1981 (Box 132, Folder 15.)
    - The New York Times Magazine – “Power, Greed and Glory on Wall Street”, February 17, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 16.)
    - The New York Times Magazine, February 24, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 17.)
    - The New York Times – “ABC is being sold”, Tuesday, March 19, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 18.)
    - The New York Times – “And Now, the Media Mega-Merger”, Sunday, March 24, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 19.)
    - The New York Times – “Sunday Business” section, September 17, 2006 (Box 132, Folder 20.)
  - Flat Box - Memorabilia
    - Wooden mount (Box 133, Folder 1.)
    - RCA paperweight in blue pouch (Box 133, Folder 2.)
    - Chart of Network, 1964-1977 (Box 133, Folder 3.)
    - Wooden Wall Street Journal plaque in small box; Goodman as Chairman, February 7, 1974 (Box 133, Folder 4.)
    - Norelco recording device (Box 133, Folder 5.)
    - Grundig Recorder in black leather case (exhibit summer 2014) (Box 133, Folder 6.)
    - Deer and owl calendar paper weight, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 7.)
    - Westar paperweight (Box 133, Folder 8.)
    - Gold pendant (Box 133, Folder 9.)
    - University of Florida diploma case (Box 133, Folder 10.)
  - Flat Box - Memorabilia
    - Photo Expo ’69 press pass (2) (Box 134, Folder 1.)
    - ‘Heidi Loves the Super Bowl’ pin (Box 134, Folder 2.)
    - Copper Pin- Ft. Worth – Honorary Chairman – Southwest Exposition, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 3.)
    - ‘The American Revolution of ’63 – I watched all 3 Hours’ pin (Box 134, Folder 4.)
    - Stamps issued by the Italian Government honoring Arturo Toscanini with letter from John F. Royal (Box 134, Folder 5.)
    - World Series ticket, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 6.)
    - New York Lottery Tickets, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 7.)
    - RCA records – Jose Feliciano (2) (Box 134, Folder 8.)
  - Flat Box - Scrapbook
    - Visit to Cincinnati, October 10 and 11, 1967 (Box 135, Folder 1.)
  - Flat Box - Doctoral Robes for Honorary Degrees
    - William Jewel University (red) (Box 136, Folder 1.)
    - (orange) (Box 136, Folder 2.)
  - Oversize – Awards - Certificates
    - Television Pioneers of America Award, May 22, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 1.)
    - Admiral of the Navy of Nebraska, January 22, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 2.)
    - The Deadline Club Hall of Fame – Sigma Delta Chi, May 20. 1975 (Box 137, Folder 3.)
    - Honored Prophet Award, June 14, 1979 (Box 137, Folder 4.)
    - Distinguished service on the Journalism Advisory Board – University of Georgia, May 17, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 5.)
  - Oversize – Awards – Plaques
    - Distinguished Kentuckian Award, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1.)
    - Distinguished Service Award – 1979 – presented by the Affiliates Executive Committee of the NBC Radio Network (Box 138, Folder 2.)
    - Kentucky Journalism Hall of Fame, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 3.)
    - George Foster Peabody Broadcasting Awards – Distinguished Service Peabody National Advisory Board, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 4.)
  - Audio Visual Material – 7” reel to reel tapes
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 1.)
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 2.)
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 3.)
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 4.)
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 5.)
    - FCC Hearings, March 12, 1969 (Box 139, Folder 6.)
- Audio Visual Material
  - Audio Cassettes
    - unlabeled cassettes (8) (Box 140, Folder 1.)
    - unlabeled cassette case (Box 140, Folder 2.)
    - The First Fabulous Fifty Show #5 (Box 140, Folder 3.)
    - W.R. McAndrew 49th Birthday, 1963 (Box 140, Folder 4.)
    - Q and A #1 (Box 140, Folder 5.)
    - Q and A #2 (Box 140, Folder 6.)
    - Whitehead News Conference (Box 140, Folder 7.)
    - RTNDA Luncheon – Noon-2PM, September 17, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 8.)
    - CBS Shareholders Meeting, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 9.)
    - Pomerante and Finkelman – Queen’s Agents (Box 140, Folder 10.)
    - CBS Stockholders meeting Mtg., Apr. 1977 (Box 140, Folder 11.)
    - CBS Stockholders Mtg., April 1977 (empty case) (Box 140, Folder 12.)
    - RCA Stockholders Meeting-- May 6, 1975 – Accuracy In the Media (3) (Box 140, Folder 13.)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Luncheon for Mr. Julian Goodman, October 23, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 14.)
    - Government and the Media, September 1973 (Box 140, Folder 15.)
    - Go Show (Box 140, Folder 16.)
    - Monitor’s final weekend (Box 140, Folder 17.)
    - KBA Distinguished Kentuckian Award Banquet for Julian Goodman, October 23, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 18.)
    - R. Wald Panel – NAB Chicago, March, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 19.)
    - Democratic Convention Pep Rally, July 11, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 20.)
    - Sports Hearings, November 2, 1977 (2) (Box 140, Folder 21.)
    - Energy Crisis, December 19, 1973 (2) (Box 140, Folder 22.)
    - NBC Radio Network Bicentennial Contest Promotion (Box 140, Folder 23.)
    - NBC Affiliates Meeting, May 17, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 24.)
    - RCA Stockholders’ Meeting – Part I, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 25.)
    - RCA Stockholders’ Meeting – Part III, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 26.)
    - Shareholders Meeting (Box 140, Folder 27.)
    - Questions and Answers Stockholder’s meeting (Box 140, Folder 28.)
    - 1956 Barkley Speech at W&L – Robert E. Bradford – Fm. Stephen Sharp, FCC, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 29.)
    - Colson (Box 140, Folder 30.)
    - J. Goodman, October 11, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 31.)
    - NBC – Fall Presentation (Box 140, Folder 32.)
  - Reel to Reel
    - Unlabeled Synchrotape (Box 140, Folder 1.)
    - Outlook – “Morgan Beatty” (Box 140, Folder 2.)
    - Morgan Beatty – News of the World, January 2, 1948 (Box 140, Folder 3.)
    - Unlabeled 3 ½ “ reel to reel (3) (Box 140, Folder 4.)
  - Books
    - Association of Radio News Analysis, 1942-1954 (Box 141, Folder 1.)
    - Four Days: The Historical Record of the Death of President Kennedy – compiled by United Press International and American Heritage Magazine (Box 141, Folder 2.)
    - Eisenhower: American Hero – The Historical Record of his Life – by the editors of American Heritage Magazine and United Press International (Box 140, Folder 3.)
    - The Inaugural Book – 1973: “The Spirit of ‘76” (Box 141, Folder 4.)